算牌人
字幕制作｜娱乐圈大雷
https://weibo.com/520d
我从没想过自己会适合蹲监狱
I never imagined myself as someone suited to a life of incarceration.
小时候，我很害怕密闭空间
As a boy, I was afraid of confined spaces.
我害怕电梯
I feared elevators.
当我足够大的时候，我只想钻进车里
When I was old enough, I just wanted to get in the car
摇下车窗，开车，开车……开车去我想去的地方
Roll the windows and drive, drive... drive wherever my eyes would take me.
我是一个美国孩子
I was an American kid.
任何形式的禁闭对我来说都是可怕的
Confinement of any kind was terrifying to me.
因此，令我惊讶的是，在被判处十年监禁后
So, to my surprise, having been sentenced to ten years in prison,
我发现自己适应得相当好
I found I adjusted quite well.
第七区全面封锁800小时
Section Seven, full lockdown, 800 hours.
我喜欢这种套路
I liked the routine.
我喜欢这种养生法
I liked the regimen.
同样的活动，同样的时间，每天
Same activities, same time, every day.
同样的牙刷，同样的衣服，同样的马桶
The same toothbrush, the same clothes, same toilet.
同样的汗，不新鲜的烟，不新鲜的尸体，不新鲜的食物，不新鲜的屁
Same stale sweat, stale smoke, stale bodies, stale cooking, stale farts.
同样的谈话
Same conversations.
面孔变化不大
The faces change but not much.
没有选择
No choice.
我发现我喜欢读书
I found that I liked reading books.
我以前从来没有读过一本书——没有从头读到尾
I'd never read a book before-- not all the way through.
我为自己找到了一种超乎想象的生活
I found a life for myself that had been beyond my imagination.
我是在监狱里学会数牌的
It was in prison I learned to count cards.
《21点》与其他游戏的不同之处在于它是基于相关事件
What separates blackjack from other games is that it's based on dependent events,
也就是说过去会影响未来的概率
Meaning past affects the probability in the future.
这房子有1.5%的优惠
The house has a 1.5% advantage.
如果牌手知道牌的性质，他就能把门牌优势转化为自己
If a player knows the nature of the cards in the shoe, he can turn the house advantage to himself.
为了做到这一点，他必须记录下每一张牌
To do this, he has to keep track of every card that is played.
计数是基于高/低系统
Count is based on a high/low system.
高牌10、j、q、king的值为- 1
High cards-- ten, jack, queen, king-- have a value of minus-one.
如果它们被耗尽，玩家的优势就会下降
If they are depleted, player's advantage goes down.
低牌，2、3、4、5、6，值为+ 1
The low cards-- two, three, four, five, six-- have a value of plus-one.
7、8和9没有计数值
The seven, eight and nine have no count value.
玩家追踪每一张卡片并计算运行计数
The player keeps track of every card and calculates the running count.
然后玩家就会得到真正的点数，也就是持续点数除以剩下的牌组数
Then the player arrives at the true count, which is the running count divided by the decks remaining.
例如，如果运行次数是+ 9，而还剩下4副半牌，那么9比4副半牌的实际数是+ 2
For example, if the running count is plus-nine and there are four and a half decks remaining, nine over four and a half gives you a true count of plus-two.
随着真实计数的增加，玩家的优势也会增加
As true count increases, the player's advantage increases.
其理念是，当你没有优势时，少赌一点，当你有优势时，多赌一点
The idea is to bet little when you don't have the advantage, more when you do.
嗯，对我来说差不多够了
Well, that's about enough for me.
-嘿，伙计，很高兴见到你-和你玩得很开心
-Hey, man, good to see you. -Good playing with you.
一次
Again.
我们是怎么做的吗?
How we doing?
-嗨你好吗?——好
- Hi. How are you? - Good.
您想要大钞吗?
And would you like large bills?
是的,请
Yes, please.
一、二、三、四、五、六、七、五十
That's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven and 50.
——750美元-谢谢
-That's $750. -Thank you.
-祝你愉快-你
-Have a good day. -You, too.
美好的一天
--Good day.
日安，先生
Good day to you, sir.
我想住一晚的单人房
I'd like a... single, one night.
我现在就支付我有现金
I'll pay now. I have cash.
- 56美元-好的
-$56. -All right.
中午结账的
Checkout's at noon.
在这里签字
Sign here.
你想喝点咖啡吗?
Would you like some coffee?
它有多久的历史了?
How old is it?
我今天早上做的
I made it this morning.
我很好
I'm fine.
房间101-谢谢
-Room 101. -Thank you.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
B先生
Mr. B.
好久不见了-嘿
-Long time, no see. -Hey.
-没那么久，狡猾的乔-你最近好吗?
-Not so long, Slippery Joe. -How you been?
不，他们不再这么叫我了
No, they don't call me that no more.
-是吗?他们叫你什么?
-Yeah? -What are they calling you?
你有什么建议吗?
Do you have a suggestion?
你是来参加扑克锦标赛的吗?
You here for the poker tournament?
是的我喜欢盛大的开幕式
Yeah. I like grand openings.
重新开放我不知道他们为什么要这么麻烦
Reopenings. You know, I don't know why they bother.
他们正在解决问题
Well, they're working things out.
会犯的错误它总是发生
Mistakes get made. It always happens.
他们新开了一间高赌注牌九房
They got a new high-stakes pai gow room.
是的，房子的几率是11%
Yeah, house odds 11%.
是啊，还有很多笨蛋
Yeah, and plenty of suckers.
我不知道那些亚洲赌徒相当狡猾
I don't know. Those Asian gamblers are pretty crafty.
不，你只是觉得他们是那样的
No, you j-just seem to think of them that way, you know.
你要玩什么?
What-what are you gonna play?
我要玩21点
I'm gonna play a little blackjack.
你知道吗，这里有很多很棒的男人
Oh, you know, there's some great guys down here.
市中心布朗…-我认识的人够多了
-Downtown Brown... -Ah, I-I've met enough people.
不，你得见见他们，伙计所以,无论如何,所以…好吧，你知道吗?我们去华沙赌场吧
No, you've got to meet 'em, man. So, anyway, so... All right, you know what? Let's just go to Washa Casino.
15分钟的路程
It's 15 minutes away.
我们可以旁听牌局
We can sit in on the poker game.
啊,滑
Ah, Slippery.
来吧，B先生
Come on, Mr. B.
我们会我们会
We're going. We're going.
你知道吗?
You know what?
这对我来说已经不存在了
This has been dead to me.
你可以…堪萨斯城对我来说也很烂
You can... Kansas City's been a bust for me anyway.
-就像，自从我…-从没在堪萨斯城玩过
-It's like, ever since I... -Never played Kansas City.
沃沙赌场，他们从哪弄来这个名字的?
Washa Casino-- where'd they get a name like that?
这是土著
It's indigenous.
嗯
Hmm.
那些印第安人的东西呢?
Well, where's all the Indian shit?
——大奖
--Jackpot.
大便
Shit.
狗屎!
Shit!
他们进入决赛了
They're down to the final table.
Mm.
他妈的世界锦标赛
World fucking tournament.
亲吻我的球
Kiss my balls.
Slip，你怎么了?
What's your problem, Slip?
我没有任何问题
I ain't got no problem.
——美国!美国!
- USA! USA!
看看这个混蛋，美国先生
Look at this asshole, Mr. USA.
这对他很有效
It's working for him.
是啊，他在拼命工作
Yeah, and he's working it for all it's worth.
他出生在乌克兰
He was born in the Ukraine.
你知道他有自己的网站吗?
You know he's got his own website?
我大老远跑来就是为了这破事
I came all the way out here for this shit.
你接下来要去哪里?
Where you on to next?
大西洋城有个执法会议
Uh, there's a law enforcement convention in Atlantic City.
gsc嗯
-GSC. -Hmm.
是啊，警察总是很好
Yeah, cops are always good.
他们喝了点酒，就觉得没人能碰他们
They get a few drinks in 'em, they think nobody can touch 'em.
——大便-我跟你说过我在帕斯卡古拉的哥哥鲍比吗?
- Shit. - I ever tell you about my brother Bobby from Pascagoula?
州警
- State trooper.
美国!美国!美国!
-USA! USA! -USA!
那人一天也没干过
The man never saw a day of service.
我真想把那面红白蓝三色的旗子从他嘴里插进去，从他屁眼里插出来
I'd like to run that red, white and blue flag straight through his mouth and out his asshole.
但你刚刚讲述了他的人生故事
But you just told the story of his life.
美国!美国!美国!美国!
USA! USA! USA! USA!
就这样,宝贝
That's it, baby.
我可以加入你们吗?
May I join you?
是我们的客人
Be our guest.
我认识你
I recognize you.
我们以前玩过-是的
-We've played before. -Yeah.
我还是让你们两个…年轻人
You know, I'm gonna let you two just... youngsters be.
我要去玩骰子
I'm gonna go play some dice.
好吧
All right.
三倍-不,四次
-Three times. -No, four times.
巴尔的摩的马蹄铁，凯撒大西洋城，福克斯伍兹和费城的哈拉斯——是对的
Horseshoe Baltimore, Caesars Atlantic City, Foxwoods -and Harrah's Philly. -That's right.
你直接朝福克斯伍兹开了一枪
You binked a gutshot straight at Foxwoods.
没有解释的运气
No explaining luck.
琳达,对吧?
Linda, right?
琳达
La Linda.
lh，就像《幸运女士》里说的那样
LL, like "Lucky Lady."
啊,好吧
Ah, okay.
我看过你的比赛
I've watched you play.
你会算牌，对吧?
You count cards, right?
我没那么聪明
I'm not that smart.
但你赢了，所以你数牌
But you win, so you count cards.
你如何避免被退让?
How do you avoid getting backed off?
我被退让了
I've been backed off.
但你还是来了
Yet here you are.
是啊，这只是程度的问题
Yeah, well, it's a matter of degree.
赌场不介意算牌的玩家
The house doesn't mind players who count cards.
他们甚至不介意那些算牌赢的玩家
They don't even mind players who count cards and win.
我要一杯汤姆·柯林斯加坦奎莱
Oh, I'll have a Tom Collins with Tanqueray.
-嗯嗯哼苏打水,请
-Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. -Soda water, please.
他们不喜欢的是那些数牌赢大钱的玩家
What they don't like are players who count cards and win big.
关键是你赢了多少钱，怎么赢的
It's about how much you win and how you win it.
我坚持适度的目标
I stick to modest goals.
这就是我想跟你说的
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name again?
威廉告诉
William Tell.
我看过你玩扑克，我想知道你为什么下这么低的赌注
I've watched you play poker, and I wonder why you play at such low stakes.
你是一个杰出的
You're a crackerjack.
我坚持适度的目标
I keep to modest goals.
不，没有理由
No, there's no reason for that.
你可以让别人投资你，也就是MTT，赚700万
You can get someone to stake you-- an MTT-- make seven million payout.
这就是你的工作，你你经营一个马厩
That's what you do-- you-you run a stable.
我一直在找纯种马
I'm always looking for a good thoroughbred.
我可以找个人百分百支持你，我保证
I can get someone to back you 100%, on my word.
我喜欢低调工作
I prefer to work under the radar.
我以为你是个赌徒
I thought you were a gambler.
-谢谢你是受欢迎的
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
-Thanks. -You're welcome.
比尔，你坐过牢吗?
So, Bill... you ever been to prison?
你为什么这么说?
Why would you say that?
我能看出来有人进去过
I can tell when someone's been inside.
这是我的天赋
It's a gift I have.
这里有个问题
Here's the problem with a backer.
他出钱，你们平分奖金
He puts up the money, you split the winnings.
这很好，但如果你输了，你必须用未来的奖金来支付这些损失
That's all good, but if you lose, you have to pay those losses out of future winnings.
对吧?这才说得通
Right? That only makes sense.
慢慢地，你的体重增加了
And slowly, you build weight.
你去任何一个扑克网站，查一下前十的赢家，有数百万的收入，他们中有50%的人都输了
You go to any poker website, look up the top ten winners-- millions in earnings-- 50% of them are underwater.
他们深陷无法偿还的债务
Swamped in debt they'll never repay.
如果你不为钱而玩，那你为什么还要玩呢?
If you don't play for money, why do you play at all?
它可以消磨时间
It passes the time.
所以,比尔……你为什么不和我一起消磨时间呢?
So, Bill... ... why don't you pass some time with me?
让我们玩扑克
Let's play poker.
在扑克游戏中，玩家不会对着庄家玩
In poker, the player does not play against the house.
他和其他选手比赛
He plays against other players.
这所房子要分一杯羹
The house takes a cut.
有两件事是必须的:
Two things are necessary:
数学概率的知识，对手的知识
knowledge of the mathematical odds, knowledge of your opponents.
扑克就是等待
Poker is all about waiting.
小时过去天过去了
Hours pass. Days pass.
一只手接一只手，每只手都像以前的手
Hand after hand, each hand like the hand before.
然后发生的事情
Then something happens.
赌徒接受资金支持会增加筹码
There's a weight a gambler can accrue by accepting financial backing.
就像一个人负债累累
It's like any weight a person in debt accrues.
它不停地建造，有自己的生命
It builds and builds, has a life of its own.
一个人也可以积累道德上的重量
There also is a moral weight a man can accrue.
这是他过去的行为造成的压力
This is the weight created by his past actions.
它是一个重量... ...它永远无法被移除
It is a weight... ... which can never be removed.
♪在我孤独的失常中……♪
♪ In my lonesome aberration... ♪
请您注意
Your attention, please.
惩教官员协会的混音台-已经被转移…-很高兴和你一起玩
The Correctional Officers Association mixer -has been moved... -Nice playing with you.
欢迎您,先生
Welcome, sir.
测谎仪历来是执法部门调查中的问题
Polygraphs have historically been the problem child of investigation in law enforcement.
这种情况可能很快就会改变
This may soon change.
Vocat电子公司开发了22点面部识别软件... ...使用专有算法与CQT检测交互
Vocat Electronics has developed a 22-point facial recognition software... ...that uses a proprietary algorithm to interact with CQT detection.
这款软件被称为STABL，目前正处于beta测试阶段
This software, called STABL, is in the beta testing phase.
Vocat将很快向合格的执法机构和公共监禁机构提供该软件的测试版本
Vocat will soon be offering a test version of this software to qualified law enforcement and public incarceration agencies.
Vocat并没有提出什么伟大的主张，但他认为这种潜在的真相探测技术的进步需要一些实地经验
Vocat makes no great claims but thinks this advance of potential truth detection needs some field experience.
它有多可靠?
How reliable is it?
它是如何工作的?
How does it work?
这就是我现在想做的
That's what I want to get into now.
我和密尔沃基警察局的志愿者一起准备了这个幻灯片演示…你还记得他吗?
I prepared this PowerPoint demonstration with a volunteer from the Milwaukee Police Department... Do you remember him?
．..误分类无辜的受试者，假阳性
...misclassifying innocent subjects, false positives.
这是我的电话号码
This is my number.
我住在这家旅馆
I'm staying at this hotel.
累积的研究证据表明，CQT识别欺骗的能力强于偶然，但错误率显著
Cumulative research evidence suggests that CQT detects deception better than chance but with significant error rates.
对于新手来说，最聪明的赌注是轮盘赌中的红/黑
The smartest bet for a novice is red/black in roulette.
你的胜率是47.4%
Your odds are 47.4%.
没有更多的押注
No more bets.
你赢了，就走开
You win, you walk away.
你输了，你就走开
You lose, you walk away.
这是赌场里唯一明智的赌注
It's the only smart casino bet.
14日,红色
14, red.
不!
No!
我的鞋在哪里?
Where's my shoe?
嘿!滚回去!
Hey! Get the fuck back!
我的鞋呢，伙计们?
Where's my shoe, guys?
鞋!
Shoe!
滚回去!
Get the fuck back!
现在!
Now!
起来!
Get up!
嗨
Hi.
尊尼获加，双份，纯的
Johnnie Walker, double, neat.
-请你明白了
-Please. -You got it.
你好
Hello.
是啊，你今晚早些时候给了我一张写着你电话的纸
Yeah, you gave me a piece of paper with your number on it earlier tonight.
你醒了吗?
You awake?
我在这里我在酒吧
I'm here. I'm at the bar.
电梯旁边的那个
The one by the elevators.
我将等待
I'll wait.
你想喝一杯吗?
You want a drink?
好吧，我也来一杯
Yeah, I'll have one of those.
另一个地方相同的
Another. The same.
确定
Sure.
我们坐
Let's sit.
这到底是怎么回事?
So, what was that all about?
什么?
What?
你给我一张写着你名字和号码的纸
You giving me a piece of paper with your name and number on it.
你还记得约翰·戈多少校吗?
You remember Major John Gordo?
当然，他已经不是少校了
Of course, he's not a major anymore.
他只是用了这个头衔
He just uses that title.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
PFC威廉·蒂利希
PFC William Tillich.
那不是你的名字吗?
Isn't that your name?
我已经做了调查
I've done my research.
我了解你的情况
I know your case.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
——是吗?-Cirk Baufort
-Who are you? -Cirk Baufort.
带有“c”的Cirk
Cirk with a "C."
我的父亲是罗杰·鲍福
My father was Roger Baufort.
戈多训练我父亲强化审讯的技巧
Gordo trained my father in the arts of enhanced interrogation.
罗杰Baufort吗?那个名字不熟
Roger Baufort? That name doesn't ring a bell.
戈多在阿布格莱布监狱
Gordo was at Abu Ghraib.
作为一个私人承包商
As a private contractor.
我父亲去那里看望了他
My father, he visited him there.
这个故事有进展吗?
Is this story going anywhere?
他的计划的美妙之处在于，一旦戈多成为一名私人承包商，他就不会因为在美国本土以外的罪行而被起诉
The beauty of his scheme was that Gordo, once he became a private contractor, he couldn't be prosecuted for crimes not on American soil.
但我父亲就没那么幸运了
But my father... wasn't so lucky.
他被开除了，吸毒成瘾
He was dishonorably discharged, got addicted to oxycodone.
他会受伤他酗酒
He'd been injured. He drank heavily.
他打我妈妈他打我
He beat my mother. He beat me.
有一天，妈妈一句话也没说就走了
My mother left one day without saying a word.
没有一个手提箱只是…
Without a suitcase. Just...
那就只剩下我了
That left only me to beat.
直到他开枪自杀
Until he shot himself.
那是四年前的事了
That was four years ago.
所以我决定就这么干了
So I decided I'd just get into it.
我自己去调查，看看到底发生了什么
Investigate it for myself, find out what really happened.
把事情讲清楚
Set things straight.
你妈妈怎么说?
What does your mother say?
她做出了选择
She made her choice.
你知道她在哪里吗?
Do you know where she is?
不
No.
我是怎么卷进来的?
And how am I involved in this?
确实有一些士兵是害群之马，他们受到了惩罚，但真正要负责任的人还在逍遥法外，在大会上发表演讲，获得荣誉学位
Well, there were a handful of soldiers that were bad apples, who were punished, but those who are really responsible are still walking around out there, giving lectures at conventions,getting honorary degrees.
这些苹果不坏
The apples weren't bad.
他们的枪管很烂
The barrel they came from was bad.
当我在约翰·戈多的研讨会上认出你的时候，我立刻就认出了你
You know, when I recognized you at John Gordo's seminar, I recognized you instantly.
我对自己说，“这个人可能想要分享我将要做的事情”
I thought to myself, "Here's a man who might want a piece of what I'm gonna do."
事情是这样开始的
This is how it starts.
只是一闪而过的想法
Just a fleeting thought.
一个白日梦
A daydream.
然后它不停地建造
Then it builds... and builds.
那是什么?
And what is that?
抓住他，折磨他，杀了他
Capture him, torture him and kill him.
他们让你当替罪羊
They made you the fall guy.
他们操了你，一等兵蒂利希
They fucked you, PFC Tillich.
-我叫泰尔-不管
-My name is Tell. -Whatever.
照片里有你没有其他人被起诉
You were in the photos. No one else was prosecuted.
只有照片里的士兵
Just the soldiers in the photos.
他们让你下地狱
They put you in hell.
然后他们怪罪于你
Then they blamed you for it.
你在莱文沃斯有兵营，戈多在科威特有一个又一个
You got the barracks at Leavenworth, and Gordo got R and R in Kuwait.
柯克，你得退后
Cirk... you need to back off.
我花了很多时间想的和你现在想的一模一样
I've spent a lot of time thinking the exact same thoughts you're thinking right now.
它们会吃掉你
They eat you up.
你要告发我吗?
Are you gonna tell on me?
不
No.
我不是
I'm not.
这是你的生活
It's your life.
带"C"的牛奶?
Cirk with a "C"?
这是比尔告诉
It's Bill Tell.
你想和我一起去吗?
You want to ride with me?
我是个玩牌的人
I'm a card player.
我从一个城市到另一个城市，从一个赌场到另一个赌场，从一个牌室到另一个牌室
I go from city to city, casino to casino, card room to card room.
它变得孤独
It gets lonely.
我想有人陪我
I'd like some company.
我来支付费用
I'll cover the costs.
是谁?
Who is it?
告诉
Tell.
比尔
Bill.
进来吧
Come on in.
你是这样生活的?
You live like this?
我在收拾行李
Well, I was packing.
好吧我们收拾好你的烂摊子，上路吧
All right. Let's get your shit together, get on the road.
关掉它
Turn it off.
啊,来吧
Ah, come on.
把那该死的关掉
Turn that shit off.
你是谁?上帝吗?
Who are you? God?
如果你真的去过那里，你这辈子就不会想再听到那些屁话了
If you'd ever actually been there, you'd never want to hear that shit again in your life.
那么，我们要去哪里?
So, where are we going?
你从没告诉过我
You never told me.
你从没问过
You never asked.
特拉华公园有场赛马
There's a racino at Delaware Park.
特拉华州的赌场与赛道相连
Delaware casinos are tied into race tracks.
我不是很喜欢打牌
I'm not really into playing cards.
你喜欢运动吗?
Do you like sports?
是的
Yeah.
他们有一本很棒的体育书
Well, they have a great sports book.
是的，但那要花钱我是说我要花多少钱?
Yeah, but that costs money. I mean... how much is it gonna cost me?
因为我不能把钱花在体育博彩上
'Cause I can't really go around spending my money like that on sports betting.
这个无礼的小混蛋是谁?
Who is this insolent little prick?
我之前确实和他们玩过幻想橄榄球，但我觉得那不算
I did play fantasy football with the guys a while back, but... I don't suppose that counts.
大学怎么样?那里发生了什么事?
What about college? What happened there?
它不适合我
It wasn't for me.
你欠了多少债?
How much debt you got?
一些
Some.
很多
A lot.
你想回去吗?
And you want to go back?
我心情不好
I got out of the mood.
你有什么兴趣爱好吗?
Do you have any interests?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
兴趣，就像你想做的任何事情:一份职业，一份生意
Interests, like... anything you want to do: an occupation, a business.
我有兴趣
I got interests.
体育博彩本身就是一个世界
Sports betting is a world unto itself.
每时每刻，世界上都有上百款游戏在进行
There's a hundred games going on around the world at any given moment.
这是大量的信息
That's a lot of information.
但这里的算法比你更快更好更快，所以除非你有内部消息，赌体育只是为了好玩
But the algorithms here at the house are faster and better and quicker than you, so unless you have inside information, sports betting is just for fun.
给你几百块钱
Here's a couple hundred bucks.
你选两队，下点赌注，找点乐子
You pick two teams, place some bets, have some fun.
我要去玩21点
I'm gonna go play some blackjack.
这是零花钱
Here's walking-around money.
等一下
Just, uh, a second.
只是外面有点吵
It's just a little damn noisy out there.
哦，好多了
Oh, that's a lot better.
拉琳达，你在吗?
Hey, La Linda, you there?
我在特拉华赛道
Uh, I'm at Delaware Raceway.
电工
Electricians.
我一直在想你说的话我又想了想
So, uh, I've been thinking about what you were saying and having some second thoughts.
我可能对你刚才说的很感兴趣
I might be interested in, uh, in what-what you were talking about.
是的，我知道
Yeah, I realize that.
我只是觉得我们可以把谈话进行到下一步
I just think that we could take the conversation to the... the next step.
之后，回到AC
After this, back up to AC.
好吧
Okay.
All right.
惩罚有尽头吗?
Is there an end to punishment?
需要付出的努力是否有一个限度?
Is there a limit to the amount of effort it takes to merit expiation?
有可能知道一个人何时达到极限吗?
Is it possible to know when one reaches the limit?
♪哦♪哦♪哦♪哦♪哦♪哦♪哦♪哦哦她来了
♪ Ooh ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪ Ooh-ooh... Well, here she is.
夫人
Madam.
加入我们的行列
Join us.
拉琳达，我想向你介绍这位年轻人以前叫柯克·博福特
La Linda, I'd like to introduce you to the young man formerly known as Cirk Baufort.
现在我们就叫他小子
Now we just call him the Kid.
是的那是" c "的Cirk
Yep. That's Cirk with a "C."
-是的-很高兴见到你，小子
-Yeah. -Pleased to meet you, Kid.
体育书籍之王，小子
King of sports book, the Kid is.
昨天，我玩了两场比赛，都被双爆了
Yesterday, played two games, hit 'em both on a double pop.
哦给我点你的运气
Oh. Give me some of your luck.
我和拉琳达有点事想和你谈谈
Uh, La Linda and I just have something we want to discuss.
顶多……-是的
-Maybe... -Yeah.
我来试试老虎机
I'll, uh, give the slots a whirl.
好吧赌小输小
All right. Bet small, lose small.
他是个好孩子
He's a good kid.
你想说的是什么?
What was this thing you wanted to talk about?
我可能想攒点钱，为了攒钱，我需要一个支持者
Uh, well, I may want to build up a nest egg, and, uh, to do that, I need a backer.
这是一个戏剧性的转变
Well, that's a dramatic turn.
你唤醒了我
You woke something in me.
我不知道
I don't know.
这是孩子他需要帮助
It's the Kid. He needs help.
钱就能做到吗?
And money will do that?
他的债务
He's got debts.
那么，我们从哪里开始呢?
So, where do we start?
那就去参加一次WSOP之旅吧
Well, jump on one of these WSOP tours.
他们每周都有活动
They got an event every week.
如果你愿意旅行，你会很快赶上来的
And you'll come up fast if you're willing to travel.
我是
I am.
我们先从东海岸开始
We'll start on the East Coast for now.
取笑他们
Tease 'em.
拉斯维加斯吗?
Vegas?
这就是钱的来源
That's where the money is.
我得去见赞助人吗?
Do I have to meet the backer?
对一些人来说，这是一种自我意识
For some people, it's an ego thing.
别人不在乎-嗯
-Others don't care. -Mm-hmm.
我会找到适合你的
I'll find something that suits you.
我攒了钱，就走人了
I build my nest egg, I bail.
最多一年，然后我就走人
One year max, then I'm out.
我希望我能相信
I wish I could believe that.
相信
Believe.
我太老了，不适合干这个
I'm too old for this.
-Mwah再见再见
-Mwah. Bye. -Bye.
有一天，你问我，“有史以来最伟大的扑克牌是哪一手?”
The other day, you asked me, "What was the greatest hand of poker ever played?"
我只能凭我亲眼所见说，这是我所见过的最好的手
And I can only speak for what I have seen, and this... is the best hand I ever saw.
2012年，爱荷华州的印度赌场
2012, Indian casino in Iowa.
奥马哈国家的黑鸟湾
Blackbird Bend, Omaha Nation.
10 k比赛
10K tournament.
Goldie——亚洲选手，戴过很多金牌——以及Alex Karesco, WSOP冠军
Goldie-- Asian player, wore a lot of gold-- and Alex Karesco, WSOP champion.
你可能听说过他
You may have heard of him.
亚历克斯有口袋皇后，梅花和方块
Alex has pocket queens, clubs and diamonds.
Goldie有八九个方块
Goldie has eight, nine of diamonds.
你是怎么做到的?
How'd you do that?
练习我在一个我有很多时间的地方
Practice. I was in a place where I had a lot of time on my hands.
现在的失败
Now the flop.
黑桃10，方块j，红桃q
Ten of spades, jack of diamonds, queen of hearts.
水里有血
There's blood in the water.
双方都认为自己领先
Both players think they're ahead.
它会检查，提高，再提高，再提高，打电话
It goes check, raise, reraise, re-reraise, call.
亚历克斯和戈尔迪正面交锋
Alex and Goldie head-to-head.
现在轮到
Now the turn.
十的钻石现在…只有一张卡能把戈尔迪救出来
Ten of diamonds. Now... there is only one card that gets Goldie out.
有百分之二的概率会出现方块7
There's a two percent chance the river will come the seven of diamonds.
亚历克斯有98%的机会赢满十的皇后
Alex has a 98% chance of winning with queens full of tens.
Goldie看着损坏的地方
Goldie looks at the damage.
他连一个赌注都没留下
He doesn't even have a pot-sized bet left behind.
发出像日本人那样的吮吸声
Makes this little sucking sound that the Japanese do.
然后他全力以赴
Then he goes all in.
亚历克斯的电话
Alex calls.
现在这条河
Now the river.
七的钻石
Seven of diamonds.
同花顺胜过满座戈尔迪获胜
Straight flush beats a full house. Goldie wins.
你看过那个游戏吗?
You saw that game?
从那以后我就没去过爱荷华州
Haven't been to Iowa since.
你能给我们加满吗?
Could you top us off, please?
这个... ...你关于约翰·戈多少校的计划，你仔细考虑过了吗?
So this, um... ... this plan you have about Major John Gordo-- you given it more thought?
他的指甲
He's all nails.
你不是
You're not.
他刚从《使命召唤》里出来
He's right out of fucking Call of Duty.
你要怎么做?
How you gonna do that?
嗯…需要一剂镇静剂
Well... there would need to be a tranquilizer.
氯胺酮与替拉唑联合使用
Ketamine, combined with Telazol.
它可以由一支飞镖手枪控制
It can be administered by a dart pistol.
你从哪儿知道的?
Where'd you find out about this?
——互联网-你有吗?
-The Internet. -And you have it?
氯胺酮
Just the ketamine.
但令人惊讶的是，这些东西是多么容易得到
But it's amazing how easy the stuff is to get.
我是说，我随便点的
I mean, I ordered it on a lark.
三天后，它来了
Three days later, it arrived.
这不是很好考虑
This isn't very well thought out.
所以我才需要一个搭档
And that's why I need a partner.
有经验的人，有专业知识的人
Somebody with experience, somebody with expertise.
和动机
And motive.
一个强大的家伙
A strong guy.
像你这样的人
A guy like you.
让我们回顾一下你的场景
Let's... roll back your scenario for a moment.
你找到约翰·戈多了
You've located John Gordo.
你用飞镖射中了他
You shot him with a dart.
他是嘎嘎
He's gaga.
下一个什么?
What next?
带他赤身裸体
Strip him naked.
给他戴上兜帽
Put a hood over his head.
一个绿色的军用沙袋
One of those green military sandbags.
你可以在eBay上找到它们
You can find them on eBay.
限制他
Handcuff him.
把他吊在天花板上，别让他睡着
Hang him from the ceiling, keep him from sleeping.
让他打飞机，我就打他的腿
Make him try to jerk off while I hit him in the legs.
你父亲跟你说过吗?
Did your father tell you about this?
不，他从来没提过
No, he never talked about it.
他把一切都藏在心里
He kept it all inside.
他打败你
He beat you.
那是过去的事了
That's in the past.
身体还记得
The body remembers.
它储存了所有的信息
It stores it all.
你想听听吗?
Do you want to hear about it?
你对此感兴趣吗?
Would that interest you?
-什么?-你知道
-What? -You know what.
你一定很想听
You're dying to hear.
噪音
The noise.
的气味
The smell.
粪便，尿，油，炸药，漂白剂，汗，烟
Feces, urine, oil, explosives, bleach, sweat, smoke.
整天，每一天
All day, every day.
沙蜘蛛，骆驼蜘蛛，蟑螂大小的蚂蚁
Sand spiders, camel spiders, ants as big as cockroaches.
热浪，恐惧，肾上腺素杰克，迫击炮
The heat, the fear, the adrenaline jack, mortars.
纯粹的噪音
The sheer noise of it.
和血液
And blood.
而生存的唯一方法就是超越
And the only way to survive was to rise above.
上升,笑
Rise and laugh.
上网疯狂
Surf the craziness.
看到一个成年人在自己身上拉屎撒尿
To see a grown man shit and piss on himself.
唱这首歌，伙计
Sing the song, man.
噪音，该死的噪音
The noise, the fucking noise.
噪音
The noise.
我们都被困在那里了，在同一个鬼地方
We were all just trapped in there, in the same shit, sh-sh... shithole.
他们和我们
Them and us.
我是在为我们的所作所为辩护吗?
And am I trying to justify what we did?
不
No.
……我们的所作所为无可辩解
Nothing... Nothing can justify what we did.
你父亲明白这一点
Your father understood that.
如果你在那里，你就能理解
If you were there, you could understand.
否则，就没有理解
Otherwise, there's no... understanding.
♬在我孤独的失常中
♪ In my lonesome aberration
♬不要乱动王冠……♪
♪ Don't meddle with a crown... ♪
明尼苏达?
Minnesota?
上次是什么时候?
When was the last time?
奥兰多吗?
Orlando?
牛津痛苦这是正确的
Oxford Downs. That's right.
-你和Clickity Dick在一起——美国!美国!
- You were with Clickity Dick. - USA! USA!
我真想杀了那混蛋
I'd like to put a cap in that motherfucker.
-慢慢来，米妮
- Now, take it smooth, Minnie.
-锻炼你的腿
- And exercise those legs.
电影之后他们叫他"明尼苏达胖子"
They call him Minnesota Fats after the movie.
现在已经没有多少胖子会玩职业扑克了
You know, there's not a lot of fat people that play professional poker anymore.
我喜欢叫他查理二下巴
I like to call him Charlie Two Chins.
这是为什么呢?
Why is that?
因为他的下巴比中国电话簿还多
'Cause he got more chins than a Chinese phone book.
谢谢你的直线
Thanks for the straight line.
明尼苏达胖子在那部电影里打台球
Minnesota Fats played pool in that movie.
-不,扑克-不，那是辛辛那提小子
-No, poker. -No, that's Cincinnati Kid.
哦,等等
Oh, whatever.
♪在我孤独的失常中……多桌锦标赛的首选扑克变体是无限制的德州扑克
♪ In my lonesome aberration... The preferred poker variant for multi-table tournaments is no-limit Texas Hold'em.
它鼓励大盆大盆的种植
It encourages large pots and large raises.
奖金由排名前五的选手平分
The prize money is split between the top five players.
在发出洞牌之前，在按钮左侧的玩家必须贴上大小百叶窗
Before the hole cards are dealt, the player to the left of the button must post small and big blinds.
这刺激了行动，每小时百叶窗就会升起
This stimulates action, and the blinds go up every hour.
♬我们现在可以见面了
♪ We can see each other now
其余的都是普通的卡片
The rest of the cards are common cards.
翻牌，三张牌
The flop, three cards.
♪像皇冠一样围绕着你
♪ Surrounds you like a crown
1800年
1,800.
♬我们现在可以见面了
♪ We can see each other now
把
The turn.
♬我们现在可以见面了
♪ We can see each other now
和河
And the river.
这条河能让输的人瞬间变成赢家
The river can instantly turn a losing hand into a winner.
那是Hold'em的赌博上诉
That's Hold'em's betting appeal.
都在
All in.
♪在我孤独的失常中……发生了什么事?你感到无聊吗?
♪ In my lonesome aberration... What happened? You get bored?
玩一些插槽
Played some slots.
你应该读一些书
You should read some books.
我给你买一个
I'm gonna buy you one.
我读过的书
I've read books.
她怎么了?
What is it with her?
- name——什么?
-Name one. -One what?
书
Book.
《傻瓜扑克》怎么样?
How 'bout Poker for Dummies.
我相信你已经读过了
I believe you may have read it.
我喜欢他
I like him.
哇你去了第二次晚餐休息时间
Wow. You made it to the second dinner break.
在我坚持那么久之前，我肯定打了二十多场比赛
I must have fired two dozen tournaments before I lasted that long.
那么，还剩下多少呢?
So, how many are left?
四张桌子，明天就该做好了
Four tables, so should be done tomorrow.
你打了多少牌?
How much cards do you play?
每小时40只手，每天8到12小时，每周6到7天
40 hands an hour, eight to 12 hours a day, six to seven days a week.
你还做其他事情吗?
Do you do anything else?
像什么?
Like what?
像任何东西
Like anything.
去公园，听音乐会，去博物馆
Go to a park, a concert, a museum.
博物馆吗?-是的
-Museum? -Yeah.
我给你买本关于它的书它叫“傻瓜博物馆”
I'll buy you a book on it. It's called... Museums for Dummies.
Ba-dum-bum
Ba-dum-bum.
不，但说真的，你应该做点别的
No, but seriously, you should do something else.
改变一下
Just for variety.
我喜欢打牌
I like playing cards.
♬在我孤独的失常中
♪ In my lonesome aberration
♪不会被人群包围…♪
♪ It won't settle with a crowd... ♪
美国!
USA!
美国!美国!美国!
USA! USA! USA!
这是800000美元
That's $800,000.
他们的钱是从哪里来的?
Where do they get their money?
天啊露易丝
Geez Louise.
慢下来,孩子
Slow down, Kid.
看到紫色筹码了吗?他们怎么说?
You see the purple chips? What do they say?
5000年
5,000.
5000是什么?
5,000 what?
5000粒大米?
5,000 grains of rice?
这不是钱
That's not money.
那些是比赛用的筹码
Those are tournament chips.
我们称它们为美元
We just call them dollars.
这是很好的宣传
It's good publicity.
那么，多少钱呢?
So, how much is it?
取决于买进和分割
Depends on the buy-in and the split.
像这样的游戏，大概有50万人在玩
A game like this, there's about 500,000 in play.
获胜者将获得150分，亚军将获得70到80分，以此类推
The winner will get 150, runner-up anywhere 70 to 80, and so on.
——哦,是的!——美国!美国!
- Oh, yeah! - USA! USA!
美国!美国!美国!
USA! USA! USA!
你知道他是谁吗?
You know who he is?
谁?
Who?
比尔·泰尔或者他的真名是什么
Bill Tell or whatever his real name is.
你知道他是谁吧?
You know who he is, right?
我只听过威廉·泰尔
All I've ever heard was William Tell.
你觉得他为什么会有另一个名字?
Why do you think he has another name?
你一直在他身边
You've been around him.
他是一个谜
He's a mystery.
我不知道这是好事还是坏事
And I don't know if that's a good thing or a bad thing.
我有危险吗?
Am I in any danger?
的什么?
Of what?
坠入爱河?
Falling in love?
别孩子气了
Don't be a child.
他的过去是什么?
What is his past?
我还没问
I haven't asked.
你们俩在一起做什么?
Well, what are you two doing together?
我没有任何目标
I don't have any goals.
我只是随波逐流，过一天算一天
I'm just along for the ride, one day at a time.
嗯
Hmm.
你觉得他手里拿着什么?
What do you think he's holding?
我不知道，但如果你保持安静，我们会知道的
I don't know, but if you be quiet, we'll find out.
都在
All in.
调用
Call.
哦,耶!美国!
Oh, yeah! USA!
美国!美国!
USA! USA!
——美国!美国!
- USA! USA!
——美国!-够了，宝贝
- USA! - That's it, baby.
好吧
All right.
一晚赚五万四千
54,000 for a night's work.
希望你不会失望
Hope you're not disappointed.
你27岁，我27岁
That's, uh, 27 for you, 27 for me.
我签个名
Let me sign this.
嘿，呃，失陪一下
Hey, uh, excuse me a second.
我去冲洗一下
Got to hose it.
好吧
All right.
我要一杯曼哈顿的
I'll have a Manhattan.
我要…相同,请
I'll have the, uh... the same, please.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
干杯干杯
-Cheers. -Cheers.
你那天说这话是什么意思?
What did you mean when you said that the other day?
说什么?
Said what?
我叫醒了你
I woke you.
这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
我不知道我只是随便说了几句
I don't know. It was just something I said.
这只是一个评论
It's just a comment.
Mm.
说起来真奇怪
It's a odd thing to say.
你有什么故事?
So, what's your story?
每个人都有故事
Everybody's got a story.
yourstory是什么?
What's yourstory?
为什么扑克?
Why poker?
让我猜猜，和一个男人有关
Let me guess-- it has something to do with a man.
宾果-这是在哪里?
- Bingo. - Where was this?
东圣路易斯
East Saint Louis.
他走出了自己的禁区
He went outside his zone.
他倾斜
He tilted.
哪个方向?
Which direction?
暴力
Violence.
但他有一些喜欢我的好朋友，他们都是赌徒，我也朝那个方向发展
But he had some good friends who liked me, and they were gamblers, and I drifted in that direction.
…他们说我有很好的人际交往能力
And... they said I have very good people skills.
是啊，我找到了我擅长的东西
Yeah, I found something I'm good at.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我喜欢我们之间的友谊
I like this friendship we have.
所以,嗯…你的计划是什么?
So, um... what are your plans?
我喜欢…我喜欢它的发展方向
I like, uh... I like where it's headed.
我的意思是今晚
I mean tonight.
我得回旅馆了
I got to go back to my motel.
我还有工作要做
I got some work to do.
你不呆在这里?
You're not staying here?
不，我不喜欢待在赌场
No, I don't like staying at casinos.
他们知道你的一切，女佣和员工
They know everything about you-- the maids and the staff.
走廊相机,噪音
Corridor cameras, noise.
不适合我
It's not for me.
回头见，拉琳达
See you down the road, La Linda.
克利夫兰,对吧?
Cleveland, right?
是的
Yeah.
他的真名是约翰·罗杰斯
His real name was John Rodgers.
“约翰·戈多”后来出现了
"John Gordo" came sometime later.
他出生在佐治亚州
He was born in Georgia.
他第一次引起中央情报局的注意是在反叛军行动期间
He first came to the attention of the CIA during the Contra counterinsurgency.
他在尼加拉瓜接受过审讯训练
He was trained in interrogation in Nicaragua.
从那里，他进入了SERE项目
From there, he entered the SERE program.
生存，逃避，抵抗和逃避
Survival, Evasion, Resistance and Escape.
这个计划是为了帮助被俘的美国士兵经受住敌对的审讯
The program was devised to help captured U.S. soldiers withstand hostile interrogations.
他妈的起来!起来!
Get the fuck up! Get up!
他们被置于压力环境中
They were put into stress conditions.
感官剥夺，封闭的空间，危险的噪音轰炸
Sensory deprivation, confinement in close spaces, given bombardment with dangerous decibels of noise.
饥饿、睡眠不足
Starvation, sleep deprivation.
和性羞辱
And sexual humiliation.
在关塔纳摩拘留营的外国战斗人员对审讯毫无反应之后，他们决定对SERE项目的教训进行逆向工程
After the foreign fighters at the Guantanamo detention camp were unresponsive to interrogations, a decision was made to reverse engineer the lessons learned in the SERE program.
SERE的心理活动指导人员被带到关塔那摩去设计强化审讯技术
SERE psych op instructors were brought to Gitmo to devise enhanced interrogation techniques.
第一批抵达的是顾问约翰·戈多(John Gordo)，他现在是一名平民
One of the first to arrive was consultant John Gordo, now a civilian.
在关塔那摩学到的教训被传达到世界各地的审讯黑狱
Lessons learned at Gitmo were conveyed to interrogation black sites around the world.
2003年，政府决定将巴格拉姆机场和阿布格莱布的平民监狱改为关塔那摩监狱
In 2003, a decision was made to Gitmo-ize the civilian prisons at Bagram Airfield and Abu Ghraib.
平民顾问约翰·戈多(John Gordo)于5月抵达
Civilian consultant John Gordo arrived in May.
你上过大学吗，蒂里希?
Did you go to college, Tillich?
社区大学，两年
Community college, two years.
他们教你创造力吗?
They teach you creativity there?
没有,先生
No, sir.
好吧，这就是它的作用
Well, that's what it takes here.
不是所有的黑白
Not everything's black-and-white.
你得发挥你的想象力
You got to use your imagination.
这不是要遵循手册
This isn't about following a manual.
这是为了得到答案
It's about getting answers.
这些答案将拯救美国人的生命
Answers that'll save American lives.
如果他们不知道答案怎么办?
What if they don't know the answers?
他们都这么说
They all say that.
这是他们的文化
That's their culture.
跟我来
Follow me.
叫醒他!
Wake him up!
博福特，进去
Baufort, get in there.
是时候谈谈了，小家伙
Time to talk, little buddy.
——了!我们走吧!
--Up! Let's go!
走吧!
Go!
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
蒂利希……我喜欢你
Tillich... I like you.
我觉得你有资格
I think you got what it takes.
你有正确的东西
You got the right stuff.
我要让你上夜班
I'm gonna put you on night shift.
那是所有好事情发生的地方
That's where all the good stuff happens.
好吧，让我们好好教训艾哈迈德!
Okay, let's fuck this Ahmed up!
格里尔把他身上的东西擦干净
Greer. Wipe that shit off of him.
你的好日子到头了，艾哈迈德
Your easy days are over, Ahmed.
来吧
Come on.
让他起来让他起来
Get him up. Get him up.
戈多是正确的
Gordo was right.
我有这个能力
I had it in me.
我有正确的东西
I had the right stuff.
小子说得对
The Kid was right.
照片一出来，戈多就消失了
When those photos came out, Gordo vanished.
照片上是唯一被起诉的人
The only ones prosecuted were in the pictures.
不是他们的上级
Not their superiors.
不是他们的上级的上级
Not their superiors' superiors.
戈多继续前行，创办了自己的咨询公司
Gordo moved on, started his own consulting company.
我听说他在开罗工作
I heard he was working in Cairo.
在军队里，军衔意味着一切
In the military, rank means everything.
在USDB，这没有任何意义
In USDB, it means nothing.
f……-你在干什么，伙计?-什么?
The f... -What you doing, man? -What?
-你有问题吗?-不我很抱歉
-You got a problem? -No. I'm sorry.
-你有问题吗?我很抱歉
-You got a problem? -I'm sorry.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
这样做这样做
Do it. Do it.
婊子
Bitch.
囚犯的名字叫克莱·威廉姆斯
Prisoner's name was Clay Williams.
我不知道他是死是活
I don't know if he's alive or dead.
如果他还活着，我想知道我是否能雇他来完成这项工作
If he were alive, I wonder if I could hire him to finish the job.
你知道，这生活也没那么糟糕
You know, this ain't such a bad life.
我想我会习惯的
I think I could get used to this.
差距很小
It's a thin margin.
这是24 - 7
It's 24-7.
大多数猫都不行
Most cats can't cut it.
你是怎么认识拉琳达的?
So, how'd you meet La Linda?
我喜欢她
I like her.
她经营一家马厩
She runs a stable.
这就是所谓的一群由投资者支持的赌徒
That's what they call a group of gamblers backed by investors.
赌徒是马
The gamblers are the horses.
投资者提供资金
The investors put up the money.
和马厩平分奖金
Split the winnings with the, uh... the stable.
但他们为什么不直接用自己的钱呢?
But why don't they just use their own money?
OPM
OPM.
别人的钱
Other people's money.
赌场，电视，网站，他们都想要大赌注
Casino, the TV, the websites-- they all want big pots.
这是娱乐
It's entertainment.
嘿，我们到底要去哪里?
Hey, where are we going, anyway?
我以为圣路易斯在那边呢
I thought Saint Louis was back that way.
绕道
Taking a detour.
我们要去回忆一下往事
We're gonna take a little trip down memory lane.
我在这里住了八年半
This was my home for eight and a half years.
既然我们在附近，我想我们可以过来看看
Since we were near, I thought we'd drop by.
在那里，二楼
Up there, second floor.
202 B Pod
202 B Pod.
第一年之后我就有了自己的住处
I got my own place after the first year.
那么,嗯…另一边的另一个地方
Then, um... another place on the other side.
记得我跟你说过的那个人吗，我想让你见的那个?
You know that fella I told you about, the one I wanted you to meet?
他在这里
He's here.
我想去拜访一下他我已经安排
Thought I'd pay him a visit. I've arranged it.
想加入吗?
Want to join?
去军事监狱?
Go into a military prison?
不不,谢谢
No. No, thanks.
就监狱而言已经很不错了
Well, it's pretty good as far as prisons go.
你知道，建于2002年
You know, built in 2002.
东西还能用，比如厕所
Things still work, like toilets.
妈的，伙计，我是说，你走进去那些门就在你身后关上了，就这样
Shit, man, I mean, you walk in there and those doors close behind you, that's fucking it.
我要在
I'm going in.
来吧就当是实地考察吧
Come on. Think of it as a field trip.
作为一个教育的时刻
As a teachable moment.
我在车里等
I'll wait in the car.
我邀请你
I'm inviting you.
我不走了
I ain't going.
把车停好
Just park the car.
嘿，你去过地球吗?
Hey, you ever been on Google Earth?
那是什么?
What is that?
我等你的时候就在那里这是惊人的
It's where I was when I was waiting for you. It's amazing.
听着，你可以进入世界上任何地方
Look, you can enter any place in the world.
它马上就出现了街景
It comes right up. Street View.
看看这个大丘路290号
Look at that. 290 Great Hills Road.
洛克维尔,弗吉尼亚州
Rockville, Virginia.
房子，环境，纬度，经度
The house, the surroundings, latitude, longitude.
那是约翰·戈多的家
That's John Gordo's house.
前门，后门
Front entrance, back entrance.
你还在想他吗?
You still got him on the brain?
是的,先生
Yes, sir.
我觉得这不是个好主意
I don't think that's such a great idea.
莱文沃斯那边怎么样?
How'd it go at Leavenworth?
你还在生我的气?
You still pissed at me?
拉琳达不是应该在这里和我们见面吗?
Hey, wasn't La Linda supposed to meet us here?
是的
Yeah.
她明天会来
She'll be here tomorrow.
我们在圣路易斯见面，然后在比洛克西做一大堆
Meet us in Saint Louis, then do a deep stacks in Biloxi.
图尼卡，然后去巴拿马城
Tunica, and on to Panama City.
你喜欢她，对吧?
You like her, huh?
是的
Yeah.
是的我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
你结过婚吗?
You ever been married?
当我在服役的时候，我是一个喜欢女人的男人
When I was in the service, I was a bit of a ladies' man.
以为我是
Thought I was.
但是,呃…然后另一件事发生了
But, uh... then the other stuff happened.
叙述被打断了
The narrative was broken.
你多久没上过床了?
So, how long's it been since you got laid?
你有多久没见过你母亲了?
How long has it been since you've seen your mother?
我不知道去哪找她
I wouldn't know where to find her.
这是废话
That's bullshit.
这关你什么事?
What business is it of yours, anyway?
你还记得她吗?-当然
-You remember her? -Sure.
是吗?她联系你了?
Yeah? She reach out to you?
她想联系你吗?
She try and contact you?
我跟你做个交易，小子
I'll make you a deal, Kid.
你去找你妈，我他妈去睡
You go see your mother, and I'll fucking get laid.
我不喜欢监狱
I don't like prisons.
即使在高速公路上看到它们，看着它，你会意识到，“哦，天哪，那是监狱”
Even seeing them on the highway here, looking at it and... you realize, "Oh, my God, that's a prison."
我爸以前从巴格拉姆给我妈写信，她会哭
My dad used to send my mom letters from Bagram, and she'd cry.
扑克中也有类似的东西
There's something quite similar in poker.
你知道"倾斜"这个词吗?
You know the phrase "tilt"?
是的
Yeah.
当一个球员想要赢球的时候，就在他的区域外打球
When a player gets caught up in winning, plays outside his zone.
就像弹球一样
Just like in pinball.
在审讯中也有类似的情况
And there's something similar in interrogations.
这叫做“力漂移”
It's called "force drift."
当审讯者对囚犯施加越来越多的力量却收效甚微时，就会出现这种情况
It happens when the interrogator applies more and more force to the prisoner with less results.
审讯者被挫败感和权力所陶醉
The interrogator becomes intoxicated by frustration and power.
任何人都可以倾斜
Any man can tilt.
我可以倾斜
I can tilt.
你父亲会倾斜
Your father can tilt.
你可以倾斜
You can tilt.
我说跟我一起去
I said ride with me.
你所做的
You did.
你走了过来
You came along.
你觉得我们在做什么，你和我?
What do you think we're up to, you and me?
♬在我孤独的失常中
♪ In my lonesome aberration
♬它不会被人群包围
♪ It won't settle with a crowd ♪
♪在我孤独的失常中……♬啦啦啦琳达，♬啦啦琳达
♪ In my lonesome aberration... ♪ La La La Linda, La La La Linda ♪
♬啦啦啦琳达
♪ La La La Linda.
——拉琳达!
--La Linda!
给，我给你提前登记好了
Here, I preregistered you with a buy-in.
现在，你的名字得到了认可
Now, your name is getting some recognition value.
嗯，这总是一件好事
Well, that's always a good thing.
——如何投票?
--How's the turnout?
-嗯,很正常-哦
-Uh, it's normal. -Oh.
你知道那个，总是这样的人吗?
You know that guy, uh, that's always doing like this?
宗教罗尼-是的他在这里
-Religious Ronnie. -Yeah. He's here.
他带着圣塔塔和那些东西
Got the Santa Tanita and all that stuff with him.
santeriasanteria……♬在我的孤独中，嗯，嗯，嗯
-Santeria. -Santeria... ♪ In my lonesome aberration Mm, mm, mm.
♬它不会被人群包围
♪ It won't settle with a crowd ♪
你是我养的一头野兽
♪ You're a beast that I was raising ♪
♪它就像一顶皇冠围绕着你♪
♪ That surrounds you like a crown ♪
♪但是我需要一些狂喜♪但是我没有什么可以展示的
♪ But I need some rapture ♪ But I got nothing to show
♪♪我的心不会碎♪不会把银子变成金子
♪ And my heart ain't broken ♪ Won't turn silver to gold
♬在你寂寞的倡导下让我们把卡片挂在空中吧!
♪ In your lonesome advocation Let's get the cards in the air!
你不能干涉皇冠
♪ You don't meddle with the crown ♪
你是被我牵着的一条皮带
♪ You're a leash that I was twisting ♪
它就像礼服一样穿在你身上
♪ And it wears you like a gown ♪
♪但是我需要一些狂喜时钟!
♪ But I need some rapture Clock!
时钟在38
Clock on 38.
♪但是我没有什么要展示的…♪
♪ But I got nothing to show... ♪
好吧,好吧
Okay, okay.
一个伟大的球员能看穿你的灵魂
A great player can see right into your soul.
他可以戴耳塞，连帽衫，棒球帽，镜子眼镜，滑雪面罩，但他能看穿你的灵魂
He can wear earplugs, a hoodie, a baseball cap, mirrored glasses, a ski mask, but he'll see right into your soul.
调用
Call.
♪♪我的心不会碎♪不会把银子变成金子
♪ And my heart ain't broken ♪ Won't turn silver to gold.
——Cirk ?-他一定是撞车了
-Where's Cirk? -He must have crashed.
我给他打电话叫醒他
I'll call him and wake him up.
不，没关系不用麻烦了
No, that's all right. Don't bother.
我想喝一杯
I want a drink.
你们都要点什么?
What can I get you-all?
我要一杯加冰的坦基莱
Uh, I'll have a Tanqueray on the rocks.
我要一杯杰克，双份，纯的
I'll have a Jack, uh, double, neat.
你和他谈谈
You talk to him.
你最近注意到他什么了吗?
Have you noticed anything about him lately?
像什么?
Like what?
穆迪和我也不知道
Moody and... I don't... I don't know.
我收到了摇滚扑克的赞助邀请
Well, I got a offer for a sponsorship from Rock Poker.
10000年,为你
10,000, for you.
是吗?就是那个乳头上有小马标志的，对吧?
Yeah? That's the one with the, uh, little pony logo on the titty, right?
是啊，带着"扑克"的摇摆木马
Yeah, the rocking horse with the word "poker."
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
是的我他妈还好
Yeah. I'm fucking all right.
“他妈的好了”
"Fucking all right."
哭了,大便
Crying and shit.
我需要做什么来获得这份赞助?
-What do I have to do for this sponsorship? -Mm.
你只需要在比赛期间穿他们的t恤就行了
You just have to wear their T-shirts during the tournaments.
我不得不问
I-I had to ask.
这是一个提议
It was an offer.
真希望那小子也在
I wish the Kid had been here.
-好吧，让我打电话给他-不，没关系
-Well, let me call him. -No, it's all right.
把他单独留下
Leave him alone.
你知道你被录取了这是属于你的时刻
You know you made the cut. This is your moment.
我觉得你误会我了
You know, I think that you have the wrong idea about me.
是的，我想赢钱
Yes, I-I want to win the money.
我想去参加世界职业棒球大赛，但仅此而已
I want to go to the World Series, but then that's it.
这个叫柯克的孩子需要帮助
This kid Cirk, he needs help.
他负债累累
He's got financial debts.
我理解他
And I understand him.
如果我能帮他，也许他还有机会重新开始，重新接受教育，开始新的生活
And if I can help him, maybe he has a chance to start over again, resume his education and start a life.
-你会那么做吗?
- And you would do all that?
嗯…是的
Well... yeah.
是的
Yeah.
你一定是我见过的最奇怪的扑克玩家
You have to be the strangest poker player I ever met.
-哦，你不知道
-Oh, you have no idea. -Mm.
你明天要做什么?你要走
What you doing tomorrow? You're off.
我没有计划
I got no plans.
她对我说:“你见过夜晚灯火通明的城市吗?”
She said to me, "Did you ever see a city all lit up at night?"
我说:“是的，我见过整个城市着火”
I said, "Yeah, I've seen a whole city on fire."
“不是那样的，”她说
"Not like that," she said.
♪嗯♪哦哦♪哦…鲍比，你一定要看看这个
♪ Mmm ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪ Oh... Bobby, you must see this.
我没有过得很糟糕
I didn't have it bad.
拜托，相信我这是惊人的
Come on, trust me. This is amazing.
那不是我想说的
That's not what I meant to say.
你当然知道别人比你更好
Of course you know other people have it better.
你要学会小心对待某些人
And you learn to be careful around certain people.
但我有朋友，当然也有家人
But I had friends, and I had family, of course.
他们有一个公园
They had a park.
他们像这样点燃它
They lit it up like this.
大得多
Much bigger.
我怎么知道?
How would I know?
我当时还是个孩子
I was just a little kid.
一切都更大
Everything was bigger.
-这是圣路易斯吗?-是的
-This was Saint Louis? -Yeah.
你知道吗，你过去是否做过坏事对我来说并不重要
You know, it doesn't matter to me if you did something bad in the past.
你可以告诉我
You can tell me about it.
嗯，我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
有什么不好的?
What could be so bad?
♪哦…我当时还是个孩子
♪ Oh... I was just a kid.
一切都更大
Everything was bigger.
就在你的脑海里
Just in your mind.
我在空间里来回游走
♪ I was drifting back in and out of space ♪
♪♪什么都没有♪♪没有更多的味道♪♪每一次靠近的呼吸♪♪
♪ There was nothing left ♪ There was no more taste ♪ Every closer breath you could ever share ♪
♪我从未迷失，你一直在那里
♪ I was never lost, you were always there ♪
♪我是你的，你是我的♪保留的每一刻，留下的每一个
♪ I was yours, you were mine ♪ Every moment kept, every left behind ♪
♪我从未迷失，在♪之间
♪ I was never lost, somewhere in between ♪
♬我在岸边，那是天堂
♪ I was on the shore, it was heaven ♪
♪哦…
♪ Ooh...
我很高兴你推荐了这个地方
I'm glad you suggested this place.
♪曾经在我的脑海里，每一根燃烧的荆棘
♪ It was in my mind, every burning thorn ♪
♬它像白天一样明亮，像炸弹一样响亮
♪ It was bright as day, it was loud as bombs ♪
你是刚刚开始的序曲
♪ You're an overture that's just started ♪
♬把我放下，直到爱升华
♪ Hold me down until love's exalted ♪
♪瞎跑瞎跑
♪ Running blind in and out of sight ♪
♬你在我唇边，你就是天堂
♪ You were on my lips, you were paradise ♪
♪我从未迷失，在♪之间
♪ I was never lost, somewhere in between ♪
♬我在岸边，那是天堂
♪ I was on the shore, it was heaven ♪
♪我们会慢慢地掉下来♪比炸弹更响♪像炸弹一样响♪你只要张开双臂♪像炸弹一样响♪像炸弹一样响♪哦哦哦♪哦哦哦♪哦哦哦
♪ We just slowly will fall ♪ Louder than bombs ♪ Loud as a bomb ♪ You just open your arms ♪ Loud as a bomb ♪ Loud as a bomb ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪ Ooh ♪ Ooh.
不!以耶稣和玛丽的名义，你对我做了什么?
No! In the name of Jesus and Mary, what have you done to me?
我什么都没对你做!
I have done nothing to you!
美国!美国!
USA! USA!
美国!美国!美国!
USA! USA! USA!
调用
Call.
嘿
Hey.
你在哪里?
Where were you?
哦，玩了会儿21点
Oh, played a little blackjack.
怎么去呢?
How'd that go?
提前出来了
Came out ahead.
好了
Nice.
你觉得怎么样?
How do you like it?
例如什么?这
-Like what? -This.
这辈子，你和我
This life... we have, you and me.
是的它很酷
Yeah. It's cool.
那是肯定的，但是……但是什么?
That's for sure, but... But what?
都一样
It's all the same.
你知道,……这是重复的
You know, it's... it's repetitive.
这是,呃…我不知道它是否真的感觉要去任何地方
It's, uh... I don't know if it really feels like it's going anywhere.
你知道的，你就这样转来转去直到你把事情解决了
Well, you know, you just go around and around until you work things out.
你感觉怎么样?
How's that going for you?
你还想过吗?
You given it any more thought?
不
No.
你要去参加世界扑克大赛吗?
You going to the World Series of Poker?
已经注册
Already registered.
这将会很酷
That'll be cool.
对，我就这样了
Yeah, that'll be it for me.
你要辞职吗?退出电路?
You gonna quit? Quit the circuit?
我已经服过刑了
I've done my time.
听着，我不知道我能不能去维加斯
Look... I don't know if... I'm up for going to Vegas.
是吗?你要保释吗?
Yeah? You gonna bail?
很晚了，你有空吗?
It's late, but you got a second?
确定
Sure.
我想给你看样东西
I want to show you something.
你有时间吗?
You have a moment?
我有个提议
I got a proposal.
到这里来跟我来
Come here. Follow me.
来吧
Come on.
你是这样生活的?
You live like this?
坐下来
Sit down.
需要什么吗?
Need anything?
一些水吗?
Some water?
不,我很好
No, I'm fine.
把沙袋套在头上怎么样?
How about... a sandbag to put over your head?
他们在eBay上出售
They sell them on eBay.
当平民承包商约翰·戈多第一次在阿布格莱布找我时，他说我需要更有创造力
When civilian contractor John Gordo first approached me in Abu Ghraib, he said I needed to be more creative.
他说我有天赋，但缺乏想象力
He said I had talent but I lacked imagination.
你同意吗?
Would you agree with that?
比尔，这他妈是怎么回事?
Bill, what the fuck is going on here?
现实生活还在继续
Real life is going on.
世界酷刑大赛
World Series of Torture.
-我要闪了……坐着别动!
-I'm gonna sp... -Stay seated!
你确定我不给你拿点水吗?
You sure I can't get you any water?
你可能会希望你后来接受了
You may wish you had accepted later.
听我说，柯克?
Do I have your attention now, Cirk?
我做了什么?我? !
Do I? Do I?!
是的
Yeah.
好
Good.
你的手指和脚趾末端的小神经和你的阴茎尖开始因恐惧而刺痛吗?
Are the little nerves at the ends of your fingers and toes and the tip of your dick starting to tingle with fear?
好
Good.
我把它放大一点
Let me enhance this a little bit.
我一直在调查你的事，姓c的柯克
I've been doing a little investigating about you, Cirk with a "C."
关于你父亲，我在阿布格莱布监狱见过他
About your father-- I did meet him at Abu Ghraib.
我撒了谎
I lied about that.
你的母亲，你的大学生活，你的法律经历
Your mother, your time in college, your scrapes with the law.
当然，这些都在网上
It's all on the Internet, of course.
我要向你求婚
I'm gonna make you a proposal.
坐起来
Sit up.
你有大约2万美元的大学贷款债务
You have approximately $20,000 in college loan debts.
20,000.
回到大学——学费、费用、避孕套等等——加起来，再加……
To go back to college-- tuition, expenses, condoms and so forth-- it adds up, so let's say another...
...8万
...80,000.
最重要的是，你还有五千美元的信用卡债务
On top of that, you've got $5,000 in credit card debt.
你妈妈，上帝保佑她，她有她的问题，她大约有3万5千美元的资不抵债，还有抵押贷款，所以我们就说4万吧
Your mama-- bless her, she's got her problems-- she's about 35 grand underwater, with the mortgage and all, so let's say 40 grand.
更见鬼的是，我们再给你1万块零花钱吧
And for the heck of it, let's throw in another ten grand pocket money.
十五万，现金，免税
That's 150 grand, cash, tax free.
这些都是你的，但有一个条件
All that's yours on one condition.
那是什么?
And what is that?
去看看你妈妈
Go see your mother.
她住在俄勒冈州的福尔河
She lives in Fall River, Oregon.
我有地址
I have the address.
我和她谈过了
I spoke to her.
当然，我没有告诉她我是谁
I didn't tell her who I was, of course.
去拜访她
Go visit her.
原谅她
Forgive her.
和她和好
Make things right with her.
还清她的债务
Clear up her debt.
告诉她你的大学计划
Tell her about your college plans.
那就让她跟我讲电话
Then put her on the phone with me.
我想听她说这些
I want to hear her say these things.
我想听到她的声音
I want to hear her voice.
你认真的吗?
You serious?
是的
Yes.
如果我没有呢?
And if I don't?
这不是一个你可以拒绝的提议
This is not a proposal you can afford to reject.
如果你骗了我，我会找到你
And if you cheat me, I'll find you.
你不希望发生这种事
You don't want that to happen.
我不喜欢名人赌博
I don't like celebrity gambling.
我喜欢匿名赌博
I like anonymous gambling.
我这么做是为了你
I did this for you.
你听到我说的了吗?
You hear what I'm saying?
是的
Yeah.
成交吗?
Do we have a deal?
是啊，我们说好了
Yeah, we have a deal.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
我们给她打个电话吧
Let's give her a call.
她现在应该还没睡
She'll still be up right now.
是的
Yeah.
♪哦…
♪ Ooh...
♪啊……
♪ Ah...
♪嗯…
♪ Mmm...
一秒!
One sec!
是谁?
Who is it?
这是威廉
It's William.
有什么事吗?我还以为我们会在坑里见面呢
What's up? Thought we were meeting in the pit.
你酷吗?-是的
-You cool? -Yeah.
是的
Yeah.
我们明天有决赛
Uh, we got final table tomorrow.
是的，不，我知道2,对吗?
Yeah, no, I know. 2:30, right?
嘿，你的伙伴呢?
Hey, where's your sidekick?
是啊，他要回家了
Oh, yeah, he had to... he had to go home.
他妈妈身体不舒服
His mom's not feeling well.
-他有妈妈?是的
- He has a mom? Yeah.
信不信由你
Believe it or not.
那么，你在想什么?
So, what's on your mind?
嗯…我走之前向柯克保证过
Um... I made a promise to Cirk before I left.
你知道的，他谈到你他喜欢你
You know, he talks about you. He fancies you.
你是说他自以为是个媒人
You mean he fancies himself a matchmaker.
我答应过他我会…把我的感受付诸行动
I promised him that I'd... act on these feelings I have.
这些对你的感觉
These feelings towards you.
哦
Oh.
我觉得你可能也有
I think you may have them, too.
我在空间里来回游走
♪ I was drifting back in and out of space ♪
♪什么都没剩下……你做什么,嗯?
♪ There was nothing left... You do, huh?
是的,我喜欢
Yes, I do.
♪每一次靠近你的呼吸♪
♪ Every closer breath you could ever share ♪
♪我从未迷失，你一直在那里
♪ I was never lost, you were always there ♪
♪我曾是你的，你曾是我的♪
♪ I was yours, you were mine ♪ Every moment kept, every left behind... ♪
被别人原谅的感觉和原谅自己的感觉是如此相似……
The feeling of being forgiven by another and forgiving oneself are so much alike...
．..试图区分它们是没有意义的
...there's no point in trying to keep them distinct.
我们还有多少时间?
How much time we got?
来看看这个
Come look at this.
什么?
What?
Cirk吗?
Cirk?
天啊，柯克，是你吗?
My God, Cirk, is that you?
-是的,妈妈是的，妈妈，是我-什么?你在哪里?
-Yeah, Mom. Yeah, Mom, it's me. -What? Where are you?
我在巴拿马城
I'm in Panama City.
嗯,发生什么事情了?
Well, what's happening?
已经很久了
It-it's been so long.
妈，我一直在想…我对你不公平
Mom, I've been thinking, and... I haven't been fair to you.
我想来看你
I want to come and see you.
…你还好吗?
Are you... are you all right?
这样持续了一段时间
So it goes on like that for a while.
有点伤感
Got a little maudlin.
她住在波特兰郊外
She lives outside of Portland.
他一两天内就会到
He'll be there in a day or two.
-他会在那里给我打电话
-He'll call me from there. -Mm.
你怎么让他这么做的?
How'd you get him to do that?
他想
He wanted to.
只是需要一个借口
Just needed an excuse.
我可能去拜访他们
I may go visit them.
我从来没打过西北队
I never played the Northwest.
欢迎来到决赛
And welcome to the final table.
你要密切注意
You keep tabs on this.
-我在等电话-嗯
-I'm expecting a call. -Mm-hmm.
——是的!
- Yes!
美国!美国!
USA! USA!
美国!
USA!
做得很好
Well done.
好吧,球员
All right, players.
这一关就到这里了
That's the end of the level.
90分钟的吃饭休息
90-minute dinner break.
你的手机响了
Your phone was buzzing.
从Cirk
It's from Cirk.
-“真希望你也在这里”
- "Wish you were here."
好了
Nice.
你还有十分钟
You got about ten minutes.
好游戏
Good game.
好游戏,男人
Good game, man.
我需要一分钟
I need a minute.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
地板上
Floor.
感谢大家来到弗吉尼亚州的罗克维尔
Thanks for joining me here in Rockville, Virginia.
瑞安·崔为您报道11点现场新闻
Ryan Choi with Eleven Alive News.
我们现在在约翰·戈多少校家的现场
We are currently on the scene of Major John Gordo's home.
现在，我们所知道的是有一名身份不明的嫌疑人持有一把弹丸手枪
Now, what we do know is that there has been a unidentified suspect that was armed with a pellet pistol.
嫌疑犯开了枪，但没有打中
The suspect fired and missed.
戈多少校还击，击毙了嫌疑人
Major Gordo returned fire, killing the suspect.
今天早些时候，我和戈多少校谈过
Earlier today, I spoke with Major Gordo.
你购买证券时以为这样的事情可能会发生，但你认为它永远不会发生
You purchase security thinking something like this might happen, but you don't think it ever will.
另一则新闻，仓库区域发生火灾来源可疑
In other news, a fire in the warehouse district of suspicious origin.
四家消防公司回应了
Four fire companies responded.
没有人员伤亡的报道，大约90分钟后，火势得到控制
There were no reported injuries, and the fire was brought under control after roughly 90 minutes.
火灾调查人员正在现场
Fire investigators are on the scene.
它是关闭的
It's turned off.
坐下吧，约翰
Come sit down, John.
别傻了
Don't be stupid.
你还记得我吗?
You remember me?
我应该吗?
Should I?
1A层，阿布格莱布监狱
Tier 1A, Abu Ghraib.
蒂利希?
Tillich?
比尔蒂利希
Bill Tillich.
从各方面考虑，你看起来很不错
You look pretty good, all things considered.
你在莱文沃斯待了多久?
How long were you in Leavenworth?
-八年半了——是一个婊子
-Eight and a half years. -That's a bitch.
你射杀的那个男孩... ...他想杀了你
That boy that you shot... ... he wanted to kill you.
我认为
I assumed that.
你训练他的父亲——他叫罗杰·博福特——就像你训练我一样
You trained his father-- his name was Roger Baufort-- just like you trained me.
他怎么了?
What happened to him?
他开枪自杀了
He shot himself.
所以是我的错?
So I'm to blame?
你的辩护太软弱了，蒂里希，你知道的
That's a pussified defense, PFC Tillich, and you know it.
我们每个人都要对自己的行为负责
We are each responsible for our own actions.
我相信
I believe that.
我们去下一个房间，你和我... ...我们将有一个戏剧性的重演
We are going to go into the next room, you and I... ... and we are going to have a dramatic reenactment.
我们中只有一个能活着出来
Only one of us will come out alive.
我要把事情做好
I'm going to make things right.
要么，约翰·罗杰斯…
Either that, John Rodgers...
..否则我就把子弹射穿你的眼球
...or I'm going to blast a bullet straight through your eyeball.
领导的方式
Lead the way.
在你之后
After you.
-我有一些香烟你想要一个吗?
- I got some cigarettes. - Do you want one?
不
No.
我也不知道
Neither do I.
谁先?
Who goes first?
我
Me.
紧急服务?
Emergency services?
我要报告一起凶杀案
I'd like to report a homicide.
大瀑布路290号
290 Great Falls Road.
我从没想过自己会适合蹲监狱
I never imagined myself as someone suited to a life of incarceration.
囚犯蒂利希
Inmate Tillich.
有人来看你了
You got a visitor.
当你沉默的眼睛无法说话
♪ When your silent eyes won't speak ♪
但你感觉不到那安静你在弹奏所有的琴弦
♪ But you can't feel the quiet ♪ And you're strumming all the strings ♪
但是除了黑暗什么都没有
♪ But there's nothing but darkness ♪
用哭泣的眼睛♪♪你只是在为自己祈祷♪
♪ With your crying eyes ♪ It's only your prayers that you're fighting ♪
但是没有星光你就看不到世界
♪ And the way is shown ♪ But you can't see the world without starlight ♪
所以你在男人的怜悯下把自己掏空了
♪ So you hollow yourself in the mercy of man ♪
你只是需要找到回家的路而已
♪ You just need something to find your way home ♪
梦想的塔尖是最美好的东西
♪ And a spire of dreams are the finest of things ♪
你只需要有人带你回家
♪ You just need someone to carry you home ♪
带你回家
♪ Carry you home♪
当你安静的眼睛无法说话
♪ When your quiet eyes won't speak ♪
却感受不到沉默
♪ But you can't feel the silence ♪
你被迫去偷
♪ And you're forced to scrape and steal ♪
直到你变成钻石
♪ Till you're nothing but diamond ♪
或者是强盗合唱团
♪ And royal kings or a choir of thieves ♪
你只是需要有人帮你找到回家的路
♪ You just need someone to find your way home ♪
有梦想的塔尖是最美好的东西
♪ A spire of dreams are the finest of things ♪
你只需要有人带你回家
♪ You just need someone to carry you home ♪
当你沉默的眼睛无法说话
♪ When your silent eyes won't speak ♪
却感觉不到安静
♪ But you can't feel the quiet
你在弹奏所有的琴弦
♪ And you're strumming all the strings ♪
但是除了黑暗什么都没有
♪ But there's nothing but darkness ♪
用哭泣的眼睛 你只是在为自己祈祷
♪ With your crying eyes ♪ It's only your prayers that you're fighting ♪
但是没有星光你就看不到世界
♪ And the way is shown ♪ But you can't see the world without starlight ♪
所以你在男人的怜悯下把自己掏空了
♪ So you hollow yourself in the mercy of man ♪
你只是需要找到回家的路而已
♪ You just need something to find your way home ♪
♬有梦想的塔尖是最美好的东西
♪ A spire of dreams are the finest of things ♪
你只需要有人带你回家
♪ You just need someone to carry you home ♪
带你回家
♪ Carry you home.♪